<FTL>


	<!--GENERIC ENCOUNTER STUFF-->

<ship name="SHIP_SCRAPPER_ALL" auto_blueprint="LIST_SHIPS_SCRAPPER_ALL">
	<destroyed load="SCRAPPER_DESTROY" />
	<deadCrew load="SCRAPPER_DEADCREW" />
</ship>

<ship name="SHIP_SCRAPPER_ELITE" auto_blueprint="LIST_SHIPS_LANIUS_ELITE_ALL">
	<destroyed load="SCRAPPER_DESTROY" />
	<deadCrew load="SCRAPPER_DEADCREW" />
</ship>

<event name="SCRAPPER_DESTROY">
	<text load="TEXT_DESTROYED_SCRAPPER" />
	<autoReward level="MED">stuff</autoReward>
</event>

<textList name="TEXT_DESTROYED_SCRAPPER">
	<text>The Scrapper Ship breaks to pieces and you scrap whatever you can</text>
	<text>The Scrapper ship is no more. You scrap what you can.</text>
	<text>The Scrappers are silent and their ship is in pieces, you scrap what remains.</text>
</textList>

<event name="SCRAPPER_DEADCREW">
	<text load="TEXT_DEAD_CREW_SCRAPPER" />
	<autoReward level="HIGH">stuff</autoReward>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_DEAD_CREW_SCRAPPER">
	<text>The ship halls, now bloodied, are empty and silent. You take your time as you pick through the vessal.</text>
	<text>The Scrappers put up a very tough fight but you are tougher.</text>
	<text>Your crew strips the remainder of the Scrapper ship.</text>
</textList>

<!--EVENT SPECIFIC ENCOUNTERS-->

<ship name="SHIP_SCRAPPER_OUTPOST" auto_blueprint="SCRAPPER_STATION">
	<destroyed load="SCRAPPER_OUTPOST_DESTROY" />
	<deadCrew load="SCRAPPER_OUTPOST_DEADCREW" />
</ship>

<textList name="TEXT_SCRAPPER_OUTPOST">
    <text>A Scrapper Outpost has been constructed in this sector. A steady flow of activity is coming and going from the station, however, no signals are being publically broadcast, indicating this to be a research or military facility.</text>
    <text>Within this sector lies a formidable Scrapper Outpost. The constant flurry of activity hints at the outpost's significance, yet the absence of any public broadcasts raises intriguing questions about its true purpose, possibly pointing towards secretive research endeavors or covert military operations.</text>
    <text>The beacon transmitting the location of the facility is a mystery. The Scrapper Outpost in this region is not boardcasting public signals on it's own, yet it would seem that they are inviting ships in with the beacon transmitting a signal.</text>
    <text>Amidst this sector, an imposing Scrapper Outpost commands attention, its presence marked by a continuous ebb and flow of activity. The absence of public broadcasts veils the outpost's true nature, leaving room for speculation.</text>
    <text>A formidable Scrapper Outpost has taken root in this sector. Could it serve as a covert hub for cutting-edge research or as a strategic military stronghold, concealed from prying eyes?</text>
</textList>

<event name="SCRAPPER_OUTPOST">
	<text load="TEXT_SCRAPPER_OUTPOST" />
	<ship load="SHIP_SCRAPPER_OUTPOST" hostile="false" />
	<changeBackground>BACK_SECTOR_SCRAPPER</changeBackground>
	<preventQuest />
	<beaconType id="map_icon_triangle_yellow" global="false">
		<color r="255" g="0" b="255" a="1" />
	</beaconType>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Engage the outpost.</text>
		<event>
			<text>It's better to shoot first and ask questions later.</text>
			<ship hostile="true" />
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK" />
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Ignore the outpost.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Assuming this is a military facility, it would be heavily armed and very difficult to breach. It would be better to avoid conflict and leave the area.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something on-board the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK" />
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event />
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_SCRAPPER_MILITARY" blue="true">
		<text>(Military Scrapper) Your scrapper taps your shoulder and requests a word.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You see what's up.
			"THIS STATION IS A MILITARY BASE! SERVED HERE! BELIEVE ARMS MANUFACTURING OR STORAGE! LOTS OF SCRAP! LOTS OF GUARDS!"
			They should at you with their typical cadance. Knowing that the outpost is indeed a military base is good to know and the appeal of raiding an arms manufactury is tempting. You ask your scrapper what they can do.
			"POSE AS TRANSFER! RAID THE ARMORY! RETURN! NO ONE WILL NOTICE!!!"</text>
			<choice>
				<text>You see nothing wrong with this plan at all.</text>
				<event>
					<text>You approach the outpost and are hailed shortly after turning your ship towards the outpost. You advise them that you are transporting an incoming transfer. They shout something about a requisition number.
					"#584154!!!" The scrapper shouts over your shoulder before you have a chance to even consider what to do. The voice from the outpost accepts the number, and your scrapper is teleported from the bridge. With the 'Transfer' complete, you return the ship to the beacon, emulating a departure.
					</text>
					<choice>
						<text>Continue...</text>
						<event>
							<text>A few minutes later you receive a communication from your scrapper indicating that they were successful in raiding the armory and are ready to be extracted. However, they will notice the teleportation, as well as you getting close enough, and also the scrapper who raided their armory is not necessarily the sneakiest.
							Something tells you this plan was not well thought out, but it is in motion now!
							You do a flyby of the outpost and beam your scrapper aboard as well as the weapon and scrap they stole.
							As anticipated, the outpost is now on high alert, and a fight is inevitable.</text>
							<choice>
								<text>Prepare for battle!</text>
								<event>
									<ship hostile="true" />
									<autoReward level="HIGH">weapon</autoReward>
									<choice hidden="true">
										<text>Continue...</text>
										<event load="COMBAT_CHECK" />
									</choice>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>This is a bad idea. Shoot them.</text>
				<event>
					<text>It's better to shoot first and ask questions later.</text>
					<ship hostile="true" />
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Continue...</text>
						<event load="COMBAT_CHECK" />
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>This is a bad idea. Let's just leave.</text>
				<event>
					<text>This is a military facility, it's better to leave it be. </text>
					<choice>
						<text>Do something on-board the ship.</text>
						<event load="STORAGE_CHECK" />
					</choice>
					<choice>
						<text>Do nothing.</text>
						<event />
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="SCRAPPER_OUTPOST_DESTROY">
	<text>The outpost has been destroyed, likely destroying any data or anything significantly valuable.</text>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event />
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="SCRAPPER_OUTPOST_DEADCREW">
	<text>The outpost lies empty, you are able to strip the entire station.</text>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event />
	</choice>
</event>

<!--
		ITEMS!!!
	Events that give items
-->
<eventList name="ITEMS_SCRAPPER">
	<event load="SCRAPPER_INTERROGATION" />
	<event load="SCRAPPER_TRINKETS" />
	<event load="SCRAPPER_SPLIT" />
	<event load="SCRAPPER_SHIPGRAVEYARD" />
	<event load="SCRAPPER_FLEETCRASH" />
</eventList>

<ship name="SHIP_SCRAPPER_SALVGUARD" auto_blueprint="SCRAPPER_GUARD">
	<destroyed load="SCRAPPER_SALVGUARD_DESTROY" />
	<deadCrew load="SCRAPPER_SALVGUARD_DEADCREW" />
</ship>

<event name="SCRAPPER_SHIPGRAVEYARD" unique="true">
	<text>You warp in to find a sprawling graveyard of ships, seemingly from a massive battle that took place an unknown time ago. You notice a number of unarmed scrapper ships roaming around the field picking at the scraps left behind. Not every vessal in the sector, however, is unarmed, as one such vessal approaches you and hails you.</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_SCRAPPER_SALVGUARD" hostile="false" />
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Answer the hail.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"GREETINGS CAPTAIN!! BY RIGHT OF SALVAGE LAW THIS IS OUR BOUNTY AND ANY TRANSGRESSION WILL BE MET WITH AGRESSION!!"</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>You want the salvage and propose a trade for access to the wreck. You explain the timeliness of your mission, and explain that you only wish to salvage a small portion of the wreck for the fee.</text>
				<event>
					<text>"REASONABLE HUMAN CAPTAIN! TRADE ACCEPTED! SENDING TERMS!</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Accept the terms. [Cost: 10~, 1{]</text>
						<event>
							<text>You transmit the resources.</text>
							<item_modify>
								<item type="fuel" min="-1" max="-1"/>
								<item type="scrap" min="-10" max="-10"/>
							</item_modify>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Send your crew out to Salvage the wrecked ship you were given access to.</text>
								<!--Rewards Crew Augment: Berserk[Increases crew damage and damage taken by 15%]-->
								<event load="SCRAPPER_SHIPGRAVEYARD_SALVAGE"/>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>It's better to not take any chances out here. Prepare to fight.</text>
				<event>
					<text>"HOW AWFUL!"</text>
					<ship hostile="true" />
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Continue...</text>
						<event load="COMBAT_CHECK" />
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Ignore the Scrapper and turn to leave.</text>
		<event>
			<text>The Scrapper Salvagers' Guard seem to acknowledge your lack of interest in the wreckage, and return to patrolling the area.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Check the storage.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK" />
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event />
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>It's better to not take any chances out here. Prepare to fight.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"HOW AWFUL!"</text>
			<ship hostile="true" />
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK" />
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>



<event name="SCRAPPER_SHIPGRAVEYARD_SALVAGE"/> <!--Rewards Crew Augment: Berserk[Increases crew damage and damage taken by 15%]-->
	<text>The salvaging team reports back and advises you that there is a large amount of scrap remaining onboard but it will take additional time to get everything. They send back a fair amount of resources and await your orders.</text>
	<autoReward level="MED">standard_no_item</autoReward>
	<choice>
		<text>Let's leave before the fleet catches up to us.</text>
		<event>
			<choice>
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>Order your team to spend more time salvaging.</text>
		<event>
			<text>The fleet catches up a bit more since you decided to spend additional time salvaging, but your team returns back with an even larger amount of resources from completely breaking down the ship.</text>
			<modifyPursuit amount="1" />
			<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
			<choice>
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
			<choice req="LIST_CREW_SCRAPPER" blue="true">
				<text>A scrapper wishes to speak with you...</text>
				<event>
					<text>One of your crew still onboard your ship advises you that something is off about this ship graveyard. "THESE SHIPS ARE UNKNOWN TO ME! DESIGNS! STRANGE! NOT TYPICAL SCRAPPER SHIPS! WE SHOULD INVESTIGATE ANOTHER HULL!!" You are not unaware that your entrance fee only bought you allowance to one ship, that you've already salvaged.</text>
					<choice>
						<text>We should take the risk and investigate investigate another hull.</text>
						<event>
							<text>You order your crew to board another ship, one of the more unknown appearing hulls. The scrapper volunteers themselves to join as they are eager to investigate it themselves. Seemingly the Scrapper guards do not notice your crew boarding another ship.</text>
							<choice>
								<text>Give your crew some time to search the ship for anything notable.</text>
								<event>
									<text>Your crew report back that they have found a previously unseen augment that can be installed on to our ship! They also found some additional resources and have been teleported back safely. However, the Scrappers have caught wind of your actions, betrayed by your decision to scrap the 2nd derelict ship a guard has detached itself from the group and has begun persuing you.</text>
									<augment name="CREW_BERSERK_MODULE"/>
									<autoReward level="LOW">standard_no_item</autoReward>
									<ship load="SHIP_SCRAPPER_ALL" hostile="true" />
									<choice>
										<text>There is no Choice but to fight now.</text>
										<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
									</choice>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice>
						<text>We better not take the risk, some mysteries are better left unsolved.</text>
						<event/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>	
</event>

<event name="SCRAPPER_SALVGUARD_DESTROY">
	<text>The guard has been destroyed. You should leave quickly before reinforcements come... Worse yet the the delay has allowed the fleet to catch up!</text>
	<autoReward level="MED">standard_no_item</autoReward>
	<modifyPursuit amount="1" />
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event />
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="SCRAPPER_SALVGUARD_DEADCREW">
	<text>The guards crew has been killed. You should leave quickly before reinforcements come... Worse yet the the delay has allowed the fleet to catch up!</text>
	<autoReward level="MED">standard_no_item</autoReward>
	<modifyPursuit amount="1" />
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event />
	</choice>
</event>

<!-- Template for more events. 
<event name="NEBULA_DYNASTY_SPLIT" unique="true">
	<text>Looks like several Dynasty ships have docked around a medical outpost, including several elite Reaper vessels. What could be going on there?</text>
	<environment type="nebula" />
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Dock.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Before you can even step aboard, a Ghost Alpha comes running but stops when they see you. Behind them follows a medical staff. "Outsiders? Unforetold, but fortuitous. Our friend here has exceeded splitting capacity, but has yet to divide out of fear. Could you provide some remedy for their caution?" You notice the Alpha is trembling, staring at you with its featureless face.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Try to talk the Alpha into splitting.</text>
				<event load="DYNASTY_SPLIT_ENCOURAGE" />
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Shelter the Alpha from the other Ghosts.</text>
				<event>
					<text>You quickly motion for the Alpha to follow, and they do so willingly. Running back to your ship, it looks like you've angered the Dynasty ships. One of their Reaper vessels is dispatched to reclaim their soldier.</text>
					<crewMember amount="1" class="phantom_alpha" />
					<ship load="SHIP_DYNASTY_ELITE_FIGHT" hostile="true" />
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Continue...</text>
						<event load="COMBAT_CHECK" />
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="mind" max_lvl="1">
				<text>(Mind Control) Subdue the Alpha.</text>
				<event>
					<text>Under the influence of the mind control, the Ghost Alpha is subdued long enough for the Dynasty medical staff to inject them full of a blue liquid that apparently begins the splitting process involuntarily. They thank you for your efficient problem solving and offer a reward.</text>
					<autoReward level="MED">drone</autoReward>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="mind" lvl="2">
				<text>(Upg. Mind Control) Force the Alpha to split.</text>
				<event>
					<text>The Alpha begins to shake more violently, and suddenly erupts into a fine mist, slowly reforming into two separate Ghosts. The twins look at each other and begin to scream, but are subdued by the confused medical staff. "What in the great nebula has occured? This is not how the process is intended to go about! I-I truly am uncertain of what to consider of this situation. These ones are not... uh... we would rather not have them in the field of battle. Have them instead."</text>
					<crewMember amount="2" class="phantom" />
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_SHELL_SCIENTIST">
				<text>(Shell Scientist) Explain the process.</text>
				<event>
					<text>You catch various odd phrases among the Shell's speech like "plasma membrane" and "rapid sub-division of the quantum something something." Does it mean anything? You're inclined to say no. Later, your Shell does indeed tell you that they made up everything they said, but it seems to register with the Alpha who finally agrees to go through with the process. The medical team pays you for your help.</text>
					<autoReward level="MED">drone</autoReward>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>We probably shouldn't get involved.</text>
				<event />
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Ignore the station.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Voluntarily putting yourself closer to the firing range of an elite Dynasty vessel doesn't sound like the best idea right now.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Check the storage.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK" />
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event />
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<eventList name="DYNASTY_SPLIT_ENCOURAGE">
	<event>
		<text>No matter how much you try, the Alpha simply won't listen to you. You give up and apologize, explaining you don't have any other way to help.</text>
	</event>
	<event>
		<text>You have no idea what you're talking about, but you try to sound as calming as possible. Your second opinion seems to coax the Alpha into submission. The staff of the station offer a paltry reward.</text>
		<autoReward level="LOW">stuff</autoReward>
	</event>
</eventList>

<event name="NEBULA_DYNASTY_TRINKETS" unique="true">
    <text>"The demons linger about... come aboard, it's safe from them here. I have many wonders aboard, maybe you'd like one?" A softly speaking Ghost waves for you to come aboard.</text>
    <environment type="nebula" />
    <choice hidden="true">
        <text>Go aboard.</text>
        <event>
            <text>You step aboard the ship, surprised to find it's full of oxygen. Around the walls are hanging various small trinkets. "These are my prized creations. Would you care for one?  Only 10 scrap..."</text>
            <choice hidden="true">
                <text>Buy a totem of war [+8% weapon fire rate].</text>
                <event load="NEBULA_DYNASTY_TRINKETS_WAR" />
            </choice>
            <choice hidden="true">
                <text>Buy an emblem of speed [+20% crew movement speed, +20% FTL recharge rate].</text>
                <event load="NEBULA_DYNASTY_TRINKETS_SPEED" />
            </choice>
            <choice hidden="true">
                <text>Buy an ingot of fortitude [+20% shield charge speed, +20% system sabotage resistance].</text>
                <event load="NEBULA_DYNASTY_TRINKETS_SHIELD" />
            </choice>
            <choice hidden="true">
                <text>No thanks.</text>
                <event />
            </choice>
        </event>
    </choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Avoid the Ghost.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You have better things to do than looking at 'wonders' right now.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Check the storage.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK" />
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event />
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="NEBULA_DYNASTY_TRINKETS_WAR">
	<text>"Heheh... just don't ask how it works." You head back to the ship, uncertain what to do with the object. You finally decide to place it on your dashboard and hope it works.</text>
	<hiddenAug>TRINKET_WAR</hiddenAug>
	<item_modify>
		<item type="scrap" min="-10" max="-10" />
	</item_modify>
</event>
<event name="NEBULA_DYNASTY_TRINKETS_SPEED">
	<text>"Heheh... just don't ask how it works." You head back to the ship, uncertain what to do with the object. You finally decide to place it on your dashboard and hope it works.</text>
	<hiddenAug>TRINKET_SPEED</hiddenAug>
	<item_modify>
		<item type="scrap" min="-10" max="-10" />
	</item_modify>
</event>
<event name="NEBULA_DYNASTY_TRINKETS_SHIELD">
	<text>"Heheh... just don't ask how it works." You head back to the ship, uncertain what to do with the object. You finally decide to place it on your dashboard and hope it works.</text>
	<hiddenAug>TRINKET_SHIELD</hiddenAug>
	<item_modify>
		<item type="scrap" min="-10" max="-10" />
	</item_modify>
</event>

<event name="NEBULA_DYNASTY_INTERROGATION" unique="true">
	<text>Looks like something important is going on nearby. You pull closer and see a group of Dynasty vessels parked around a disabled Auto-ship, shouting at it with their weapons charged.</text>
	<environment type="nebula" />
	<ship load="SHIP_AUTO_DYNASTY_INTERROGATION" hostile="false" />
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Ask them what's happening.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"We have captured the demon! Hark, yet it speaks not. Speak foul beast, speak! By the command of the Prime Reaper, we demand ye speak!"</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>That's an Auto-ship...</text>
				<event>
					<text>The Ghost's 'head' swivels to face you. "Huh? What garble do you speak?"</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>It's not alive. It's just a machine.</text>
						<event load="DYNASTY_INTERROGATION_TALK" />
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_ENGINEER">
				<text>(Engineer Crew) Interface with the Auto and "make it speak".</text>
				<event>
					<text>Your engineer remotely access the Auto-ship and powers it online. Fortunately, its vocal module is still active. "OooOooOoOoh! You have captured me. You are now cursed! If you do not give the Federation all of your scrap, your children will be stillborn and your crops will be plagued. OooOoOoOoooOh!" The Ghosts suddenly go into panic, scrambling for a weapon, until they realize you're a Federation ship. Desperate not to be cursed, they give you all of their scrap.</text>
					<autoReward level="MED">scrap_only</autoReward>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="hacking" lvl="2">
				<text>(Upg. Hacking) Interface with the Auto and "make it speak".</text>
				<event>
					<text>You stealthily deploy your hacking module onto the Auto-ship and power it up. Fortunately, its vocal module is still active. "OooOooOoOoh! You have captured me. You are now cursed! If you do not give the Federation all of your scrap, your children will be stillborn and your crops will be plagued. OooOoOoOoooOh!" The Ghosts suddenly go into panic, scrambling for a weapon, until they realize you're a Federation ship. Desperate not to be cursed, they give you all of their scrap.</text>
					<autoReward level="MED">scrap_only</autoReward>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Leave them to it.</text>
				<event>
					<text>These Ghosts don't seem to realize the Auto-ships can't speak. At least, not unless programmed to. Sentient Auto-ships? That's silly...</text>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Avoid them.</text>
		<event>
			<text>This looks pretty serious, and it's probably safest not to interlude.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Check the storage.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK" />
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event />
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<eventList name="DYNASTY_INTERROGATION_TALK">
	<event>
		<text>The Phantom merely laughs you off. "This is why we do not seek the help of the Federation for matters such as this."</text>
	</event>
	<event>
		<text>Before the Ghosts can respond, suddenly the Auto-ship powers on. Looks like the Ghosts didn't do a good job of disabling it... and you'll have to help them or run!</text>
		<ship hostile="true" />
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Continue...</text>
			<event load="COMBAT_CHECK" />
		</choice>
	</event>
</eventList>

-->

<!--Older stuff that may need reworked or removed-->

<ship name="SCRAPPER_SHOP" auto_blueprint="SCRAPPER_SHOP">
	<destroyed load="SCRAPPER_SHOP_DESTROYED" />
	<deadCrew load="SCRAPPER_SHOP_DEADCREW" />
</ship>

<eventlist name="SCRAPPER_ENCOUNTER_LIST">
	<event load="SCRAPPER_ENCOUNTER_SUPPORT"/>
	<event load="SCRAPPER_ENCOUNTER_HUNTER"/>
	<event load="SCRAPPER_ENCOUNTER_CORVETTE"/>
	<event load="SCRAPPER_ENCOUNTER_SHOP"/>
</eventlist>

<eventlist name="SCRAPPER_ENCOUNTER_LIST_NOSHOP">
	<event load="SCRAPPER_ENCOUNTER_SUPPORT"/>
	<event load="SCRAPPER_ENCOUNTER_HUNTER"/>
	<event load="SCRAPPER_ENCOUNTER_CORVETTE"/>
</eventlist>

<event name="SCRAPPER_ENCOUNTER_SHOP">
	<text>A scrapper vessel is in this sector. It's broadcasting a signal simply asking for scrap. Perhaps they mean to trade?</text>
	<ship load="SCRAPPER_SHOP" hostile="false" />
	<beaconType id="map_icon_store_scrapper" global="true">
		<color r="255" g="65" b="254" a="1" />
	</beaconType>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Attack them!</text>
		<event>
			<text>"EXCUSE ME?!? WE WILL STRIP THE SCRAP FROM YOUR BLOATED CARCASS!"
			It seems a boarding party has entered your ship. Maybe they had a super shield bypass?</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/>
			<boarders min="2" max="2" class="scrapper_soldier" />
			<boarders min="1" max="1" class="scrapper_medic" />
			<boarders min="1" max="1" class="scrapper_heavy" />
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK" />
			</choice>
		</event>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Hail them and see if they would like to trade.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"WE NEED SCRAP!" </text>
			<store>SCRAPPER_NORMAL_STORE</store>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice req="LIST_CREW_SCRAPPER" blue="true" hidden="true">
		<text>Your scrapper waves his hands and sends a signal to the scrapper ship; "C0UPON COD3!!!" He types in a short code and you notice the store prices drop!</text>
		<store>SCRAPPER_NORMAL_STORE_DISCOUNT</store>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="SCRAPPER_ENCOUNTER_SUPPORT">
	<text>A scrapper support ship is in this sector. It seems to not notice you, or it does and it does not care.</text>
	<ship load="TC_SCRAPPER_SUPPORT" hostile="false"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Attack the ship before it gets any bright ideas.</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK" />
			</choice>
	</choice>
	<choice req="LIST_CREW_SCRAPPER" blue="true" hidden="true">
		<text>Consult your scrapper.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Your scrapper advises you that the support ship seems to be lost. It is supposed to be with others, as part of a fleet, but this one is alone. They may need help but may find themselves unable to ask. 
			Your scrapper tells you that it would be good to hail them, as scrappers typically only care about 1 thing and are generally not overly hostile to aliens or humans.</text>
			<choice hidden="true" blue="true">
				<text>Hail the scrapper support ship and offer assistance.</text>
				<event>
					<text>The Scrapper captain responds to you with a bit of a flustered tone, "HAPPY T0 S33 FL3SHY C@PTA!N WE ARE IN NEED 0F R3PA!RS!! C@N Y0U SPARE SCR@P!!???"</text>
					<text>It seems that the scrapper does indeed only have 1 thing on its mind.</text>
					<choice req="LIST_CREW_SCRAPPER" blue="true">
						<text>Ask your Scrapper what they think.</text>
						<event>
							<text>Your Scrapper tells you that the Scrapper captain sounds genuine, but you can never be too sure since, of course, he's asking for Scrap.
							But if you are able to help someone, don't you think you should?</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Transfer the Scrapper some scrap to help facilitate their repairs.</text>
									<event>
										<text>You send over the scrap...</text>
										<item_modify> 
											<item type="scrap" min="-35" max="-35"/>
										</item_modify>
										<choice hidden="true">
											<text>Continue...</text>
										</choice>
											<event>
												<text>"THANK Y0U CAPTAIN! WE CAN OPERATE OUR ENGINES AGAIN!! TAKE FANCY MACHINE WE FIND"</text>
												<autoReward level="HIGH">augment</autoReward>
											</event>
									</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Order your crew to prepare for battle!</text>
					<event>
						<ship hostile="true"/>
						<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Continue...</text>
						<event load="COMBAT_CHECK" />
					</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Leave them alone.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Leave them alone.</text>
		<event/>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="SCRAPPER_ENCOUNTER_HUNTER">
	<text>A scrapper vessel is in this sector. It gives you no warning before powering it's weapons. It hails you, screaming something about scrap.</text>
	<ship load="TC_SCRAPPER_HUNTER" hostile="true"/>
		<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event load="COMBAT_CHECK" />
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="SCRAPPER_ENCOUNTER_CORVETTE">
	<text>A scrapper vessel is in this sector. It gives you no warning before powering it's weapons. It hails you, screaming something about scrap.</text>
	<ship load="TC_SCRAPPER_CORVETTE" hostile="true"/>
		<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
			<event load="COMBAT_CHECK" />
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="TC_SCRAPPER_CORVETTE_DESTROYED">
	<text>The scrapper vessel explodes leaving behind a large amount of scrap.</text>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">augment</autoReward>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="TC_SCRAPPER_CORVETTE_DEADCREW">
	<text>The scrapper vessel is empty, giving you ample time to scrap the ship.</text>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard_no_item</autoReward>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="TC_SCRAPPER_HUNTER_DESTROYED">
	<text>The scrapper vessel explodes leaving behind a large amount of scrap.</text>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">augment</autoReward>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="TC_SCRAPPER_HUNTER_DEADCREW">
	<text>The scrapper vessel is empty, giving you ample time to scrap the ship.</text>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard_no_item</autoReward>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="TC_SCRAPPER_SUPPORT_DESTROYED">
	<text>The scrapper vessel explodes leaving behind a large amount of scrap.</text>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">augment</autoReward>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="TC_SCRAPPER_SUPPORT_DEADCREW">
	<text>The scrapper vessel is empty, giving you ample time to scrap the ship.</text>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard_no_item</autoReward>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
	</choice>
</event>

</FTL>