<event name="ECHELON_MERCHANT_MEETUP">
	<text>Upon arriving at the beacon, you see a strangely colored ship that's similar to a Militia ship. The ship also displays a strange logo with the words "Ad Astra" on it. What should be the next action?</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_ECHELON_MERCHANT" hostile="false"/>
  	<variable name="tc_found_echelon" op="set" val="1"/>
	<choice>
		<text>Approach. They seem friendly enough.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Before you can even turn your ship to face them, the ship's captain immediately speaks to you. "You! You must be the Renegade the federation sent, right?"</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Yes, why?</text>
				<event>
					<text>"Finally! We've been taking way too much time looking for you!" the ship's teleporter system immediately beams you loads of supplies and their crew come to patch you up.</text>
					<item_modify>
						<item type="scrap" min="100" max="100"/>
						<item type="fuel" min="10" max="10"/>
						<item type="missiles" min="10" max="10"/>
						<item type="drones" min="10" max="10"/>
					</item_modify>
          			<damage amount="-15"/>
					<choice>
						<text>Sweet!</text>
						<event>
							<text>"Oh yeah, by the way. We also would like you to present you a special offer to make a "Echelon Renegades" club membership account!"</text>
							<choice>
								<text>A....what?</text>
								<event>
									<text>"Oh it's nothing much, just sign up, do tasks and stuff and get rewards like our ships! Best part of all that is the entire thing is free! Would you like an account now?"</text>
									<choice>
										<text>Yes, do make one for us please.</text>
										<event>
											<text>"With pleasure!" The intern immediately begins typing out the credentials for you, you're not sure how they got it, presumable from the federation database? "And that should be it! Don't forget to check mission and have fun with your sign-up award!" You noticed that a file for a small ship's blueprints have popped up in your database, maybe this'll be of use soon.</text>
											<unlockCustomShip silent="false">PLAYER_SHIP_AUTOGUNBOAT</unlockCustomShip>
										</event>
									</choice>
									<choice>
										<text>No thanks, we're good.</text>
										<event>
											<text>"Alright then, see you again soon!"</text>
										</event>
									</choice>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>


  	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Maybe it's best the vessel is left alone.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You decided that the strange vessel isn't worth the time, you eventually part ways with it. You can't help but wonder what things they might have.</text>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<ship name="SHIP_ECHELON_MERCHANT" auto_blueprint="ECHELON_MEETUP_MERCHANT">
	<destroyed load="DEFEAT_MILITIA_ELITE"/>
	<deadCrew load="DEFEAT_MILITIA_ELITE"/>
</ship>