<metadata>
  <title><![CDATA[ TRASH COMPACTOR COLLECTION]]></title>
  <threadUrl><![CDATA[https://github.com/Dalvest/TCC]]></threadUrl>
  <author><![CDATA[ Zuggo, Dalvest, Enchanter, Cryntolov, Ashley, NitronEXE, LandGreen, Choosechee, ConMan]]></author>
   <version><![CDATA[ 1.1 ]]></version>
  <description>
<![CDATA[
Adds lots of new weapons, amazing ships, diverse races and variations and a new questline - plenty of things are waiting to be found in the abandoned sectors of the Multiverse.
TRACKER sends his regards.

- Adds the Scrapper race, a new race of lanius that you can attach scrap to to upgrade them. (just talk to them!)
- Custom made ships such as the "Fiare Vechi", "Corossus" and "Reactive Compactor". 
- Reccuring Trash Compactor boss fight with cool new loot and increasing rewards for each fight. Once you get a certain augment in the first sector, you can summon the TC whenever at a storage check.
- The Transmitter is now a hidden aug! There is now NO reason you shouldn't get it (please!)
- PROTOGENS! FTL always needed cool floofy robots!

Coming soon: a second questline, the RECLAIM & SALVAGE ASSOCIATION, Black Rose the android renegade, Scrapper Graveyard and more!
P.S. The protogen spritesheet exists as an outline - if you wish to fill it in and include it in the mod, please give Dalvest a DM. Thanks! 

There's a lore doc in mod-appendix too, btw.

Very big thanks to (in no particular order):
Cyrus106 - Helped with most of the addon's code.
Marcrusian, Felipe - consultancy, shading, advice.
Lex - VERY comprehensive playtesting and feedback. Honorary badge of TCC.
The Ghost Hugger and Kommandant Julk - bug fixing and code sanity checks + KommJulk's inferno core thingy
GenGibs, GLAIVE, and their creator, Epirasque - all of the gibs.
GO BALLISTIC and R4V3-0N - permission to use GB-related assets and lore.
Wabbles - Banner sketches of the Trash Eater and Scrappers. Nom.
Zandoware - Did like playtesting and code stuff idk
Alder - this mod now includes Alder's amazing Instant Flair addon
Skye - helped with my sanity, I think, also made the RSA_technician recolor
Vertaalfout - coding and bugfixing help plus the migration to github!

Good Luck! Don't get compacted!

Changelog:

Update 1.1
- GITHUB page (link's up above!)
- SCRAPPERS! A new subfaction of Lanius with a pretty fun backstory.
- The RAPTOR's Right Hand flak, Raptor LMG, Lance Antipersonnel, SCRAPFLAK, Unscrapflak, Rescrapflak, RSA TAGGER and MINICANNON and Deconstructor Beam + a few others I can't recall rn;
- Loads of playable ships such as the hastily put-together Corossus, the civilian-spec The Original and the boarding madness of Razormind
- Fixed several animations such as the singularity and the tear gas. Yes, I added tear gas to FTL. Fight me. (I've got tear gas, I'll win.)
- Merged with the Bomb Flaks mod, bringing said bomb flaks (+ a new bomb flak 3 sprite as well as a conservative b. flak and a drone b. flak) and their related events into this mod - the old bomb flak was rebranded into Explosive Flak.
- Merged with Kivie Takeover, bringing in the Kivies as RSA Kivie Grunts, as well as the Laser Centrifuge weapon (so far!). Stay tuned for more Kivie Takeover stuff.
- Removed the impostor, regrettably... Added sus_death.png in the img/ folder to compensate for the loss of sus-ness.
- Added remade sprites for ships such as the Armored Wasp, The Original and Reactive Compactor thanks to ConMan.

Update 1.09.5
- remade the Reactive Compactor sprite with a new miniship and cloak image
- new drone images

Update 1.09
- added the Armored Wasp made by Dalvest
- completely reworked the Reactive Compactor and added a custom artillery for it, the MFK battery
- removed the among us themed placeholders
- made scrap transmitter hidden and fixed it

Update 1.08.5
- added the Singularity Projector made by Enchanter
- reworked the SDM transport shuttle

Update 1.08
- added playable Scrapper ship, "Fiare Vechi"
- added gibs made with GenGibs
]]>
  </description>
</metadata>
