<metadata>
  <title><![CDATA[ TRASH COMPACTOR COLLECTION]]></title>
  <threadUrl><![CDATA[https://discord.gg/YdEAngWpkr]]></threadUrl>
  <author><![CDATA[ Zuggo, Dalvest, Enchanter, Cryntolov, Ashley, NitronEXE, LandGreen, Choosechee, ConMan, Kommandant_Julk, Vertaalfout, Robinthedragon, NewtonsFourth, Pedrosian96, SillySillyMan, DemonFusionGamer, JamesTripleQ]]></author>
   <version><![CDATA[ 1.2 BETA ]]></version>
  <description>
<![CDATA[
Mod Type: Major Content Pack

NEW WEAPONS
    Singularity Projectors, big gatling guns, Flaks of all kinds, sizes and shapes and so much more!

NEW SHIPS
    Featuring the Scrapper Lanius ship line as well as Protogen Project, Avali, RECLAIM and SALVAGE, Echelon Shipyards and MORE!
    Also featuring the Extraelite packs - hunt down specific targets with specific, high-powered setups!

NEW RACES
    Lanius Scrappers, Protogens, Avali, Sergals, Sentient Robots, Kivies and Tabaxis join the fight!

NEW SECTORS AND EVENTS
    Avali Collective Sector (Avali and Protogen friendly sector) coming really soon!

Includes the following mods: Kivie Takeover, Bomb Flaks, Instant Flair, Leah Gaming, Relic Revival and RSC (heavily modified).
LOAD BEFORE FORGEMASTER AND AFTER INFERNO-CORE! THEY ARE OPTIONAL BUT HEAVILY RECOMMENDED!

TRACKER sends his regards.

Very big thanks to (in no particular order):
Cyrus106 - Helped with most of the addon's code.
Lex - VERY comprehensive playtesting and awesome feedback. Honorary badge of TCC honor.
The Ghost Hugger - bug fixing and code sanity checks
GenGibs, GLAIVE, and their creator, Epirasque - all of the gibs plus some technical help. Check out GenGibs if you haven't already!
GO BALLISTIC and R4V3-0N - permission to use GB-related assets and lore.
Wabbles - Banner sketches of the Trash Eater and Scrappers. Nom.
Zandoware - Did like playtesting and code stuff idk
Alder - this mod now includes Alder's amazing Instant Flair addon
Skye - helped with my sanity, I think, also made the RSA_technician recolor
Protosteel - a few weapon sprites from the rebel weapons pack
Robinthedragon2 - funny birb mod, aka Avali, which we've assimilated
NewtonsFourth - funni leah mod, aka Leah Gaming, which we've assimilated (clearly a "the Thing" (1982) reference)
mr_eazy_money - a few sprites from Arsenal+, thanks a lot for 'em
The Forgemaster Team - Inferno-Core compatibility for the addon installed icon
Maddiedoktor - Scrapper and Avali music
Sallyspartan, Untitled - RSC assets

Good Luck! Don't get compacted!
]]>
  </description>
</metadata>
