<metadata>
  <title><![CDATA[ TRASH COMPACTOR COLLECTION]]></title>
  <threadUrl><![CDATA[https://discord.gg/YdEAngWpkr]]></threadUrl>
  <author><![CDATA[ Zuggo, Dalvest, Enchanter, Cryntolov, Ashley, NitronEXE, LandGreen, Choosechee, ConMan, Kommandant_Julk, Vertaalfout, Pedrosian96]]></author>
   <version><![CDATA[ 1.1 ]]></version>
  <description>
<![CDATA[
Mod Type: Major Content Pack

Adds lots of new weapons, amazing ships, diverse races and variations and a new questline - plenty of things are waiting to be found in the abandoned sectors of the Multiverse.
Now includes several other mods such as Kivie Takeover, Bomb Flaks, Instant Flair, FEDERATION SPECIAL FORCES and Leah Gaming.
TRACKER sends his regards.

LOAD AFTER FORGEMASTER AND INFERNO-CORE! THEY ARE OPTIONAL BUT HEAVILY RECOMMENDED!

- Adds the Scrapper race, a new race of lanius that you can attach scrap to to upgrade them. (just talk to them!)
- Reccuring Trash Compactor boss fight with cool new loot and increasing rewards for each fight. The Transmitter is now a hidden aug! There is now NO reason you shouldn't get it (please!)
- PROTOGENS! FTL always needed cool floofy robots! Also Avalis, and soon Tabaxi, because we really need more furries. Cuteness overload!
- There's a (WIP) lore doc in mod-appendix!
- Crossover content with Forgemaster! Speaking of, you should check out Go Ballistic as well!
- Absorbed several other mods and improved each and every one of them - for example, the all-new upgradeable Sentient Robotto race!
- Ported several ships/weapons to HS/MV, such as the Stalwart Defense, the Potential and the Sovereign Star

Coming soon: a second questline, the RECLAIM & SALVAGE ASSOCIATION, Black Rose the android renegade, Scrapper Ship Graveyard sector and so much more!

Very big thanks to (in no particular order):
Cyrus106 - Helped with most of the addon's code.
Lex - VERY comprehensive playtesting and feedback. Honorary badge of TCC.
The Ghost Hugger - bug fixing and code sanity checks
GenGibs, GLAIVE, and their creator, Epirasque - all of the gibs plus some technical help. Check out GenGibs if you haven't already!
GO BALLISTIC and R4V3-0N - permission to use GB-related assets and lore.
Wabbles - Banner sketches of the Trash Eater and Scrappers. Nom.
Zandoware - Did like playtesting and code stuff idk
Alder - this mod now includes Alder's amazing Instant Flair addon
Skye - helped with my sanity, I think, also made the RSA_technician recolor
Protosteel - a few weapon sprites from the rebel weapons pack
Robinthedragon2 - funny birb mod, aka Avali, which we've assimilated
NewtonsFourth - funni leah mod, aka Leah Gaming, which we've assimilated (clearly a "the Thing" (1982) reference)
mr_eazy_money - a few sprites from Arsenal+, thanks a lot for 'em
The Forgemaster Team - Inferno-Core compatibility for the addon installed icon
Maddiedoktor - Scrapper and Avali music

Good Luck! Don't get compacted!
]]>
  </description>
</metadata>
